[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":43057,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":58037,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":45125,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":103163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":14182,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":117347,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2431,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":119779,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3656,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":123435,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1048,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":124484,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your  result. )","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5150,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":129635,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":975,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":130611,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2640,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":133251,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2  because  1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":935,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":134187,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3407,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":137594,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":984,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":138579,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the fi rst numb er, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2631,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":141211,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":951,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":142163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2351,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":144515,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1007,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":145523,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3007,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":148531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":942,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":149474,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2823,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":152298,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":927,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":153226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subt ract 6 t o get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3912,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":157139,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":910,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":158051,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":25143,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":183196,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":94357,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":277555,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":283075,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1055,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":284131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":286899,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1046,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":287946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse  of 3 und er +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2055,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":290002,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":976,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":290979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2296,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":293275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":984,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":294259,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":7088,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":301347,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":975,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":302323,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":30431,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":332755,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a g enerator  under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":72247,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":405003,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5382,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":410387,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1081,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":411468,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a ge nerator  under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3094,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":414563,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":91319,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":505883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (R emember,  a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":31055,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":536939,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":13401,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":550341,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3965,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":554308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":12831,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":567139,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":18743,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":585883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4664,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":590548,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1007,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":591556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3183,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":594740,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6935,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":601676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":11877,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":613556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3109,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":616667,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":7056,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":623724,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12- 0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5, because 4+1 is less than 9.","response_history":["5, because 4+1 is less than 9."],"rt":21439,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":645164,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3, because 8+4 = 12 but 12 is larger than 9 so it becomes 12-9=3.","response_history":["3, because 8+4 = 12 but 12 is larger than 9 so it becomes 12-9 ","3, because 8+4 = 12 but 12 is larger than 9 so it becomes 12-9=3."],"rt":27975,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":673140,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you go t your a nswer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 is the identity under 9 because number in the range of 0-9 can create 0 with another pair.","response_history":["0 is the identity under 9 because every combin","0 is the identity under 9 because ever","0 is the identity under 9 because eve","0 is the identity under 9 because ev","0 is the identity under 9 because e","0 is the identity under 9 because number ca","0 is the identity under 9 because number c","0 is the identity under 9 because number in the range of 0-9 can create 0.","0 is the identity under 9 because number in the range of 0-9 can create 0 g","0 is the identity under 9 because number in the range of 0-9 can create 0 with a ","0 is the identity under 9 because number in the range of 0-9 can create 0 with another pair."],"rt":102974,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":776115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the  inverse  of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":12087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":788203,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":3927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":792131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2919,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":795051,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6, because in order to get 0 from 3, we need to add 6 to it.","response_history":["6, because 6+3 = 9 but 9 is not lower than 9 so we subtract 9 from 9 to get","6, because 6+3 = 9 but 9 is not lower than 9 so we subtract 9 fr","6, because 6+3 = 9 but 9 is not lower than 9 so we subtract 9 f","6, because 6+3 = 9 but 9 is not lower than 9 so we subtract 9 ","6, because 6+3 = 9 but 9 is not lower than 9 so we subtract 9","6, because 6+3 = 9 but 9 is not lower than 9 so we subtract ","6, because 6+3 = 9 but","6, because in order to get 0 from 3, we need to add 6 to it."],"rt":70543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":865595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, 2+2 = 4,\n2+2+2 = 6\n6+2 = 8\n1+2 = 3\n3+2 = 5\n5+2 =  7\n7+2  = 0\n0+2 = 2\n2+","response_history":["yes, because 2+2","yes, 2+2 = 4,\n2+2+2 = 8\n2+2+2+2 = 1\n1+2 = 3\n3+2 = 5\n5+2 = 7\n7+2 = 0\n0+2 = 2\n2+","yes, 2+2 = 4,\n2+2+2 = 6\n2+2+2+2 = 1\n1+2 = 3\n3+2 = 5\n5+2 = 7\n7+2 = 0\n0+2 = 2\n2+","yes, 2+2 = 4,\n2+2+2 = 6\n6+2 = 1\n1+2 = 3\n3+2 = 5\n5+2 = 7\n7+2 = 0\n0+2 = 2\n2+","yes, 2+2 = 4,\n2+2+2 = 6\n6+2 = 8\n1+2 = 3\n3+2 = 5\n5+2 = 7\n7+2 = 0\n0+2 = 2\n2+"],"rt":218931,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1084527,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because 3+3 = 6, 6+3 = 0\n0+3 = 3\n3+3 = 6","response_history":["No, becu","No, because 3+3 = 6\n6+3 = 0\n0+3 = 3\n3+3 = 6","No, because 3+3 = 66+3 = 0\n0+3 = 3\n3+3 = 6","No, because 3+3 = 6,6+3 = 0\n0+3 = 3\n3+3 = 6","No, because 3+3 = 6, 6+3 = 0\n0+3 = 3\n3+3 = 6"],"rt":68731,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1153259,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7, 7+5 = 3, 3+5 = 8, 8+5 = 4, 4+5 = 0 ","response_history":["Yes, because  ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1\n1+5 = 6\n6+5 = 2\n2+5 = 7\n7+5 = 3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 11+5 = 6\n6+5 = 2\n2+5 = 7\n7+5 = 3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1,1+5 = 6\n6+5 = 2\n2+5 = 7\n7+5 = 3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6\n6+5 = 2\n2+5 = 7\n7+5 = 3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 66+5 = 2\n2+5 = 7\n7+5 = 3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6,6+5 = 2\n2+5 = 7\n7+5 = 3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2\n2+5 =  7\n7+5 =  3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 22+5 = 7\n7+5 = 3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2,2+5 = 7\n7+5 = 3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7\n7+5 = 3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 77+5 = 3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7,7+5 = 3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7, 7+5 = 3\n3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7, 7+5 = 33+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7, 7+5 = 3,3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7, 7+5 = 3, 3+5 = 8\n8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7, 7+5 = 3, 3+5 = 88+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7, 7+5 = 3, 3+5 = 8,8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, becaus e 5+5 =  1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7, 7+5 = 3, 3+5 = 8, 8+5 = 4\n4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7, 7+5 = 3, 3+5 = 8, 8+5 = 44+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7, 7+5 = 3, 3+5 = 8, 8+5 = 4,4+5 = 0 ","Yes, because 5+5 = 1, 1+5 = 6, 6+5 = 2, 2+5 = 7, 7+5 = 3, 3+5 = 8, 8+5 = 4, 4+5 = 0 "],"rt":138999,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1292259,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because it can only make 3, 0 and 6 but can't make the rest of the numbers in the range.","response_history":["No, because it can only make 3, 0 and 6 but can't mai","No, because it can only make 3, 0 and 6 but can't make the rest of the numbers in the range."],"rt":73784,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1366044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":21601,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1387645,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+(n - x) - n = 0","response_history":["1+_n)","1+_n","1+_","1+(","3+(n-3) - n = 0","1+(n-3) - n = 0","1+(n-1) - n = 0","1+(n - x) - n = 0"],"rt":506766,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1894412,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inver se of an  element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then we would just subtract x from n  because the returned value would equal 5 if it were added together and would mean it would be 0 under the operation.","response_history":["n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then the inverse would be 2.. ","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then the i","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then the ","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then the","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then th","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then t","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then n - x would","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then n - x woul","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then n - x wou","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then n - x wo","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then n - x w","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then n  - x =  5  - 3 = 2.","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then we would just sube","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then we would just subtract x from n  because the returned value would be","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then we would just subtract x from n  because the returned value would b","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then we would just subtract x from n  because the returned value would w","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then we would just subtract x from n  because the returned value would equal 5 if it were added together and would mean it would be 0.","n-x because if n was 5 and x was 3, then we would just subtract x from n  because the returned value would equal 5 if it were added together and would mean it would be 0 under the operation."],"rt":321463,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2215876,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know i f an ele ment x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is divided by x without any remainders, then it is not a generator. Except for 1. ","response_history":["I didn't spot any patterns, but i'm","I didn't spot any patterns, but i'","I didn't spot any patterns, but i guess there is otherwise it wouldn't be asked. ","I didn't spot any patterns, but m ","I didn't spot any patterns, but ma ","I didn't spot any patterns, but may ","I didn't spot any patterns, but mayb ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe  ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe i ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe it  ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe it ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe i ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if i ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it  ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if  it d "," I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it di ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it div ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divi ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divid ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides  ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides in ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides int ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into  ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into t ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into th ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the  ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n  ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n wi ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n wit ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n with ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n withou ","I didn't  spot any  patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without  ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without a ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without an ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any r ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any re ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any rem ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any rema ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remai ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remain ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remaind ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainder ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders ","I didn't spot any pa tterns,  but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders,  ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, t ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, th ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, the ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, then i ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, then it i ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, then it is  ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, then it is no ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, then it is not a g ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, then it is not a ge ","I didn't spot any pattern s, but m aybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, then it is not a gen ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, then it is not a gener ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, then it is not a genera ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, then it is not a generat ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, then it is not a generato ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if it divides into the n without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if x divides into the n without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if  without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns,  but may be if n  without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n i without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n ix without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n i without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is  without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is d without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is di without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is div without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is divi without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot  any pat terns, but maybe if n is divid without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is divide without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is divided without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is divided  without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is divided b without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is divided by without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is divided by  without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is divided by x without any remainders, then it is not a generator ","I didn't spot any patterns, but maybe if n is divided by x without any remainders, then it is not a generator. Except for 1. "],"rt":186039,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2401916,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":21334,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2423252,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":15094,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2438347,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remai nder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":28368,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2466716,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generator of +_6 we start with 3+_6 3 = 0, 0+_6 3 = 3, 3+_6 3 = 0.","response_history":["I rh","I r","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again to ","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again to","I think it is correct because if x divides even ly into  n then it would loop around again t","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, 3","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, 3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, i3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in 3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in ch3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in che3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n  then it  would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in chec3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in check3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checkin3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking i3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again star ting at  0. for instance, in checking if 3  +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 i +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is  +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a  +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a g +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop  around  again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a ge +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a gene +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a gener +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a genera +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generat +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generato +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generator +_6","I  think it  is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generator o +_6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generator of +_6 we start with 3+3 6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generator of +_6 we start with 3+3 = 6 ","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generator of +_6 we start with 3+3 = 6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generator of +_6 we start with 3+3 = ","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, i n checki ng if 3 is a generator of +_6 we start with 3+3 =","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generator of +_6 we start with 3+3 ","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generator of +_6 we start with 3+3","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generator of +_6 we start with 3+_6 3 = 0, 0+3","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generator of +_6 we start with 3+_6 3 = 0, 0+_6 3 = 3, 3+_6 3 = 6","I think it is correct because if x divides evenly into n then it would loop around again starting at 0. for instance, in checking if 3 is a generator of +_6 we start with 3+_6 3 = 0, 0+ _6 3 = 3 , 3+_6 3 = 0."],"rt":150462,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2617180,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":44278,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2661460,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"becase 1 is always a generator of n so the inverse of 1 could by any other number in the range but not all the numbers in th e range  would be a generator.","response_history":["becase 1 is always a geneto","becase 1 is always a genet","becase 1 is always a generator of n so the inverse of 1 could by any other number in the range but not all the numbers in the range wu","becase 1 is always a generator of n so the inverse of 1 could by any other number in the range but not all the numbers in the range would be a generator."],"rt":42846,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2704307,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":88656,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2792964,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We woul d like t o ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2439,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2795404,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"28","response_history":["28"],"rt":3245,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2798651,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2080,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2800732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Calculus I","response_history":["Calculus I"],"rt":11400,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2812133,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":8686,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2820820,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2824364,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":6696,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2831061,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"mu lti","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2391,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2833453,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat"],"rt":3494,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2836948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1912,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2838861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native  languag e(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["Enl","English"],"rt":7582,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2846444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.","response_history":["Y","No, but I did use a did","No, but I did use a digia","No, but I did use a digital","No, bu","No, b","No, ","No,","No."],"rt":27863,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2874308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The enter key made it so that it would push the continue button. This messed up my responses a couple times  because  I tried to enter a new line and it progressed me to the next screen.","response_history":["The t","The enter key made it so that it would push the continue button. This mis","The enter key made it so that it would push the continue button. This mi","The enter key made it so that it would push the continue button. This messedup","The enter key made it so that it would push the continue button. This messedu","The enter key made it so that it would push the continue button. This messed up my responses a couple times because I trid","The enter key made it so that it would push the continue button. This messed up my responses a couple times because I tried to enter a new line.","The enter key made it so that it would push the continue button. This messed up my responses a couple times because I tried to enter a new line and it progressed me toth","The enter key made it so that it would push the continue button. This messed up my responses a couple times because I tried to enter a  new lin e and it progressed me tot","The enter key made it so that it would push the continue button. This messed up my responses a couple times because I tried to enter a new line and it progressed me to th ","The enter key made it so that it would push the continue button. This messed up my responses a couple times because I tried to enter a new line and it progressed me to the next screen."],"rt":51552,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2925860,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]